Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Trustees and Administration, 1960-1978
  - Trustees — D, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.36)
  - Trustees — E, 1973 (Folder 9.37)
  - Trustees — F, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.38)
  - Trustees — H, 1974 (Folder 9.39)
  - Trustees — J, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.40)
  - Trustees — M, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.41)
  - Trustees — O, 1973 (Folder 9.42)
  - Trustees — P, 1973 (Folder 9.43)
  - Trustees — R, 1973 (Folder 9.44)
  - Trustees — S, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.45)
  - Trustees — T, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.46)
  - Trustees — V, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.47)
  - Trustees — W, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.48)
  - Board of Trustees Report of Proceedings, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.49)
  - Annual Regents Conference on Leadership Roles of Trustees, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.50)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.51)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.1)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1973 Oct (Folder 10.2)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1973 Dec (Folder 10.3)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes, 1974 Feb (Folder 10.4)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes (with attachments), 1974 May (Folder 10.5)
  - Budget Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.6)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, 1973 Oct (Folder 10.7)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, 1974 Apr (Folder 10.8)
  - Allocations Committee: Sub-Committee of Budget Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.9)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.10)
  - Trustee Committee on Coeducation, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.11)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.12)
  - Governance, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.14)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.15)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.16)
  - Joint Trustee-AAVC Committee on Coordinate Fund Raising, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.17)
  - Trustee Committee on Student Life, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.18)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.19)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 Nov (Folder 10.20)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.21)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1973 (Folder 10.22)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1974 (Folder 10.23)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.24)
  - Vice-President for Administration — Report to Trustees, 1973-1975 (Folder 10.25)
  - College Finances, 1971-1972 (Folder 10.26)
  - Comptroller, 1973-1975 (Folder 10.27)
  - Parking (Walking Campus), 1973 (Folder 10.28)
  - Agenda, 1974-1975 (Folder 10.29)
  - Agenda and Amendments, 1973-1974 (Folder 10.30)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1972-1973 (Folder 11.1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.2)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.3)
  - Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 Apr (Folder 11.6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 Mar (Folder 11.7)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1975 May (Folder 11.8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1974 Sep (Folder 11.9)
  - Faculty and Studies — Decisions, 1973 (Folder 11.10)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.11)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.12)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.13)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee — Working Papers, 1975 Jun (Folder 11.14)
  - Educational Administration Budget, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.15)
  - Faculty Salary Budget Recommendations, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.16)
  - Material Presented to Faculty and Studies Committee Meeting, 1974 Jan (Folder 11.17)
  - Faculty and Studies Material — Board Meeting, 1974 Feb (Folder 11.18)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1974 May (Folder 11.19)
  - Educational Administration Budget, 1975-1976 (Folder 11.20)
  - Faculty Salary Budget Recommendations, 1975-1976 (Folder 11.21)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1975 Jan (Folder 11.22)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1975 Feb (Folder 11.23)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee — Decisions, 1974 (Folder 11.24)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1975 May (Folder 11.25)
  - Faculty and Studies Report, 1975 Jun (Folder 11.26)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.27)
  - Investments and Finance, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.28)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.29)
  - President’s Reports, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.30)
  - President’s Report, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.31)
  - Trustee Minutes, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.32)
  - Trustee Minutes, 1974-1975 (Folder 11.33)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1973-1974 (Folder 11.34)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.1)
  - Joint Trustee-AAVC Committee on Coordinate Fund Raising, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.2)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.3)
  - Catlin Report, 1970 (Folder 12.4)
  - Trustee Committee on Student Life, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.5)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.6)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.7)
  - Trustees — B, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.8)
  - Trustees — C, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.9)
  - Trustees — E, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.10)
  - Trustees — F, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.11)
  - Trustees — G, 1974; (empty) (Folder 12.12)
  - Trustees — H, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.13)
  - Trustees — J, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.14)
  - Trustees — M, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.15)
  - Trustees — O, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.16)
  - Trustees — R, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.17)
  - Trustees — S, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.18)
  - Trustees — T, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.19)
  - Trustees — V, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.20)
  - Trustees — W, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.21)
  - Legal Counsel (Carroll Wainwright), 1974-1975 (Folder 12.22)
  - Annual Regents Conference on Leadership Roles of Trustees, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.23)
  - Report of Proceedings — Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.24)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.25)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes, 1974 Oct (Folder 12.26)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes, 1974 Dec (Folder 12.27)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes (with attachments), 1975 May (Folder 12.28)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1974 (Folder 12.29)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1975 (Folder 12.30)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.31)
  - Budget Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.32)
  - The Financial Picture of Vassar College, 1973 (Folder 12.33)
  - Coeducation — Background File, 1973-1974 (Folder 12.34)
  - Coeducation Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.35)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1975 Feb (Folder 12.36)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1975 Feb (Folder 12.37)
  - Trustee Development Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.38)
  - Vassar Development Committee, 1975 (Folder 12.39)
  - Trustee “Development Policy” Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 12.40)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1975 (Folder 12.41)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1974 (Folder 13.1)
  - Trustee Committee on Governance, 1974-1975 (Folder 13.2)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1974-1975 (Folder 13.3)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.4)
  - Trustees — B, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.5)
  - Trustees — C, 1975 (Folder 13.6)
  - Trustees — D, 1975; (empty) (Folder 13.7)
  - Trustees — E, 1975 (Folder 13.8)
  - Trustees — H, 1975 (Folder 13.9)
  - Trustees — F, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.10)
  - Trustees — G, 1975-1977 (Folder 13.11)
  - Trustees — J, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.12)
  - Trustees — O, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.13)
  - Trustees — P, 1975 (Folder 13.14)
  - Trustees — S, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.15)
  - Trustees — T, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.16)
  - Trustees — W, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.17)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 1974-1975 (Folder 13.18)
  - Joint AAVC-Trustee Meeting Minutes (with Attachments), 1975 Sep (Folder 13.19)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting Minutes (with Attachments), 1975 Oct (Folder 13.20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1975 Dec (Folder 13.21)
  - Board of Trustee — Minutes, 1975 Dec (Folder 13.22)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting, 1976 Feb (Folder 13.23)
  - Minutes of Conference with Faculty Committee, 1976 Feb (Folder 13.24)
  - Board of Trustees — Minutes, 1976 Feb (Folder 13.25)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting — Joint Task Force Report, 1976 Mar (Folder 13.26)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 May (Folder 13.27)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1975 (Folder 13.28)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1976 (Folder 13.29)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.30)
  - Report of Proceedings, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.31)
  - Board of Trustee Minutes, 1976 May (Folder 13.32)
  - Budget Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.33)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.34)
  - Trustee Development Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.35)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.36)
  - Trustee Committee on Governance, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.37)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.38)
  - Nelson Report, 1975-1976 (Folder 13.39)
  - Nelson Report, 1976 (Folder 14.1)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.2)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.3)
  - Proxy Review Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.4)
  - Trustee Committee on Student Life, 1975 (Folder 14.5)
  - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting — Notes and Minutes, 1975 Sep (Folder 14.7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes — Record of Mail Vote, 1976 Jun (Folder 14.8)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.9)
  - Coordination of AAVC and College Development Office Fund Raising, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.10)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee Meeting, 1976 Jun (Folder 14.11)
  - Amended and Accepted Report of Joint Task Force, 1976 Mar (Folder 14.12)
  - Agenda and Amendments, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.13)
  - Agenda and Amendments, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.14)
  - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.15)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.16)
  - Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 14.17)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.18)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee (paper for meeting which was postponed), 1976 Feb (Folder 14.19)
  - Faculty and Studies Report, 1976 Feb (Folder 14.20)
  - Faculty Salary Budget Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.21)
  - Educational Administration Budget, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.22)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1976 May (Folder 14.23)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1976 Jun (Folder 14.24)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee Report, 1976 Oct (Folder 14.25)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.26)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1977 Mar (Folder 14.27)
  - Faculty and Studies Reports — Decisions, 1977 May (Folder 14.28)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.29)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.30)
  - President’s Reports, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.31)
  - President’s Reports, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.32)
  - Report of Proceedings — Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.33)
  - Trustee Minutes, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.34)
  - Trustee Minutes, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.35)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1975-1976 (Folder 14.36)
  - Trustee Lists and Dates, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.37)
  - Trustees — B, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.38)
  - Trustees — D, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.39)
  - Trustees — F, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.40)
  - Trustees — H, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.41)
  - Trustees — O, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.42)
  - Trustees — P, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.43)
  - Trustees — S, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.44)
  - Trustees — W, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.45)
  - Notes in re Purcell, 1971-1975 (Folder 14.46)
  - Chairman of the Board, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.47)
  - Board of Trustees — Agenda, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.48)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 Oct (Folder 14.49)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.50)
  - Paper circulated in re Extended Sessions of Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 Oct (Folder 14.51)
  - President’s Report, 1977 Feb (Folder 14.52)
  - Saturday Board, 1977 May (Folder 14.53)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.54)
  - Report of Proceedings — Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 14.55)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1976 (Folder 15.1)
  - Development Policy Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.2)
  - Vassar College-AAVC Development Coordinating Council, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.3)
  - Budget Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.4)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, 1976 Sep (Folder 15.5)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.6)
  - Trustee Development Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.7)
  - Executive Committee — Notes and Minutes of Meeting, 1976 Sep (Folder 15.8)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.9)
  - Executive Committee — Notes and Minutes of Meeting, 1976 Dec (Folder 15.10)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1976 Dec (Folder 15.11)
  - Background Information for Affirmative Action Report to the Trustees, 1976 Dec (Folder 15.12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 Feb (Folder 15.13)
  - Executive Committee — Notes and Minutes of Meeting, 1977 Mar (Folder 15.14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 Apr (Folder 15.15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977 May (Folder 15.16)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.17)
  - Governance Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.18)
  - Trustee Committee on Governance, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.19)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.20)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1976-1977 (Folder 15.21)
  - Trustee Personnel Committee, 1977 (Folder 15.22)
  - Trustee Committee on Student Life, 1977 (Folder 15.23)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.24)
  - Vice President for Administration — Report to Trustees, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.25)
  - Joint College Committee on Long Range Financial Projections, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.26)
  - Joint College Committee: Chronological file, 1975 (Folder 15.27)
  - Long-Range Financial Planning Committee — Chronological file: Faculty salary freeze, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.28)
  - Comptroller, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.29)
  - Comptroller’s Report to the Vice President, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.30)
  - Department of Halls, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.31)
  - Director of Special projects, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.32)
  - Personnel Officer, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.33)
  - Director of Plant Operations, 1975-1976 (Folder 15.34)
  - Confidential File on Search for Director of Development, 1973 (Folder 16.1)
  - Vice President of Development, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.2)
  - Vice President for Development — Reports to Trustees, 1975-1977 (Folder 16.3)
  - Vassar College Development Reports, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.4)
  - AAVC/Trustee Joint Committee: Consultants, 1975 (Folder 16.5)
  - College/AAVC, 1974-1975 (Folder 16.6)
  - Coordination of AAVC and College Development Office, 1973-1975 (Folder 16.7)
  - New York City Development Office, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.8)
  - Fund Raising Do’s and Dont’s (Confidential), 1973 (Folder 16.9)
  - Major Prospects Lists, 1974-1975 (Folder 16.10)
  - Delma Vander Veer, 1973-1974 (Folder 16.11)
  - Vassar Today, 1974 Oct (Folder 16.12)
  - Vassar Today, 1975 Oct (Folder 16.13)
  - Chaplain, 1973-1974 (Folder 16.14)
  - Chaplain, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.15)
  - College Center, 1975 (Folder 16.16)
  - Director of Financial Aid, 1973-1976 (Folder 16.17)
  - Admissions — Candidates for Directorship, 1975 (Folder 16.18)
  - Office of Admission, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.19)
  - Richard W. Moll — Director of Admission, 1975 (Folder 16.20)
  - Committee on Admissions, 1973-1974 (Folder 16.21)
  - Office of Admission, 1976-1977 (Folder 16.22)
  - Director of Admission (Mr. Stephenson), 1973-1975 (Folder 16.23)
  - Dean of Residence, 1973-1976 (Folder 16.24)
  - Candidates: Director of Residence, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.25)
  - Public Relations — News Office, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.26)
  - Office of Public Relations — News Releases, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.27)
  - Office of Public Relations — News Releases, 1976-1977 (Folder 16.28)
  - Public Relations Candidate, 1976 (Folder 16.29)
  - Vassar Views, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.30)
  - Vassar Views, 1976-1977 (Folder 16.31)
  - Acting President (Dean Wells), 1974 (Folder 16.32)
  - Miss Wells — Entertainment and Travel Expenses — Acting President, 1974 (Folder 16.33)
  - Assistant to the President (G. Gregory Fahlund), 1975-1976 (Folder 16.34)
  - Elizabeth Daniels — Acting Dean of Faculty, 1977-1978 (Folder 16.35)
  - Assistant to the President — Marla MacKenzie, 1976-1977 (Folder 16.36)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1973-1975 (Folder 16.37)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1974-1975 (Folder 16.38)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.39)
  - Dean of Faculty — Reports to Trustees, 1973-1975 (Folder 16.40)
  - Dean of the Faculty — Reports to Trustees, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.41)
  - Registrar, 1973-1976 (Folder 16.42)
  - Dean of Studies (Mrs. Marshall), 1974-1975 (Folder 16.43)
  - New Dean of Studies: Committee to confer with President, 1975 (Folder 16.44)
  - Dean of Studies (Colton Johnson), 1975-1976 (Folder 16.45)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1974 (Folder 16.46)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1973-1978 (Folder 16.47)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.48)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Candidates, 1975 (Folder 16.49)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1973-1975 (Folder 16.50)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1974-1975 (Folder 16.51)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1975-1976 (Folder 16.52)
  - Career Planning., 1973-1974 (Folder 16.53)
  - Director of Campus Activities, 1974-1977 (Folder 16.54)
  - Search for Director of Development, 1973 (Folder 16.55)
  - Director of Development, 1973-1974 (Folder 17.1)
  - Director of Development, 1974-1976 (Folder 17.2)
  - Director of Development — Reports to Trustees, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.3)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.4)
  - Dean of Faculty — Reports to Trustees, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.5)
  - Acting Dean of Faculty (E. Daniels), 1977-1978 (Folder 17.6)
  - Acting Deanship (E. Daniels), 1976-1977 (Folder 17.7)
  - Search Committee – Dean of Faculty, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.8)
  - Registrar, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.9)
  - Dean of Studies, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.10)
  - Dean of Freshmen, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.11)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.12)
  - Vice President for Administration — Report to Trustees, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.13)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.14)
  - Vice President for Administration — Report to Trustees, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.15)
  - Proxy Review Committee, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.16)
  - Proxy Review Committee, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.17)
  - Financial Picture — Budget Priorities, 1975 Apr (Folder 17.18)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.19)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.20)
  - Comptroller, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.21)
  - Comptroller, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.22)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to the Vice President, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.23)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to the Vice President, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.24)
  - Applicants for Student Affairs, 1974-1976 (Folder 17.25)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1975-1978 (Folder 17.26)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Reports to Board of Trustees, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.27)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Report to Trustees, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.28)
  - Career Planning, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.29)
  - Chaplain, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.30)
  - Vice President for Development — Report to Trustees, 1976-1977 (Folder 17.31)
  - Joan E. Doyle, Project Manager, Office of Communications, 1977 (Folder 17.32)
  - Vice President for Development — Reports to Board of Trustees, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.33)
  - Office of Vice President for Development, 1976-1978 (Folder 17.34)
  - Office of Communications — Vassar Views, 1977-1978 (Folder 17.35)
  - Community Breakfast, 1977 Nov (Folder 17.36)
  - Budget, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.37)
  - Department of Halls, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.38)
  - Personnel Office, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.39)
  - Director of Plant Operation, 1974-1975 (Folder 17.40)
- Series II. Buildings and Grounds, 1960-1974
  - Barbour House, 1968 (Folder 18.1)
  - Noyes II, 1966 (Folder 18.2)
  - Pratt House, 1968-1969 (Folder 18.3)
  - Raymond Avenue — Widening of roadway and Faculty Housing Project, 1961-1970 (Folder 18.4)
  - Main Building, 1973 (Folder 18.5)
  - Olmsted Hall, 1971-1974 (Folder 18.6)
  - Olmsted Hall Dedication, 1974 Oct (Folder 18.7)
  - Prentiss Field, 1974 (Folder 18.8)
  - Student Housing — Terrace Houses, 1971-1974 (Folder 18.9)
  - Terrace Houses — Dedication of Father’ House, 1972 (Folder 18.10)
  - Student Housing — Town Houses on the Murphy Farm, 1971-1972 (Folder 18.11)
  - Students’ Building, 1960-1963 (Folder 18.12)
  - Student’s Building — Dining Center Dedication, 1972-1973 (Folder 18.13)
  - Experimental Theater Building, 1964-1969 (Folder 18.14)
  - Experimental Theater Building, 1968-1971 (Folder 18.15)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs — Residence, 1969 (Folder 18.16)
  - Vassar Dormitory Rehabilitation Study, 1972 (Folder 18.17)
  - Theater Wing, 1965-1966 (Folder 18.18)
  - Hallie Flanagan Davis Theater Dedication, 1973 (Folder 18.19)
  - Hallie Flanagan Davis Powerhouse Theater, 1971-1973 (Folder 18.20)
  - Campus Traffic Patterns, 1971 (Folder 18.21)
  - Dr. Baldwin’s House, 1964 (Folder 18.22)
  - Biology Building, 1965-1970 (Folder 18.23)
  - Space Requirements — New Biology Building, 1965 (Folder 18.24)
  - Computer Center: Building, 1966 (Folder 18.25)
  - Science Library, 1968-1970 (Folder 18.26)
  - Murphy Farm, 1967-1976 (Folder 18.27)
  - Municipal Skating Rink, 1973 (Folder 18.28)
  - Student Housing — Dormitory Rehabilitation, 1972 (Folder 18.29)
  - Polshek Study for Student Housing, 1972 (Folder 18.30)
  - Consulting Architect, 1964-1972 (Folder 18.31)
  - Architects (Names Suggested), 1968 (Folder 18.32)
  - Arts Center, 1969-1971 (Folder 18.33)
  - Baldwin House, 1960-1973 (Folder 18.34)
- Series III. Faculty, 1955-1978
  - Salary Budget: Department Recommendations — Faculty and Educational Administration, 1964-1965 (Folder 19.1)
  - Educational Administration, 1964-1965 (Folder 19.2)
  - Budget Requests, 1964-1965 (Folder 19.3)
  - Budget, 1965-1966 (Folder 19.4)
  - Departmental Recommendations for Faculty Salary Budget, 1965-1966 (Folder 19.5)
  - Recommendations for Educational Administration, 1965-1966 (Folder 19.6)
  - Budget Requests, 1965-1966 (Folder 19.7)
  - Budget, 1966-1967 (Folder 19.8)
  - Computer Budget Numbers — Chart of Accounts, 1966-1967 (Folder 19.9)
  - Departmental Recommendations for Promotions and Terminations, 1966-1967 (Folder 19.10)
  - Departmental Recommendations, 1966-1967 (Folder 19.11)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Folder 19.12)
  - Departmental Recommendations for Promotions and Terminations, 1967-1968 (Folder 19.13)
  - Faculty Salary Budget Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Folder 19.14)
  - Administrative Departmental Salary Budget Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Folder 19.15)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book I — Anthropology-History, 1970-1971 (Folder 19.16)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book II — Italian – Interdepartmental, 1970-1971 (Folder 19.17)
  - Faculty Salary Budget Recommendations, 1970-1971 (Folder 19.18)
  - Departmental Recommendations — Reappointments, Terminations, Promotions, 1970 Apr (Folder 19.19)
  - Departmental Recommendations for Reappointments, Promotions, and Terminations, 1970 Oct (Folder 20.1)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book I — Anthropology-German, 1970 Dec (Folder 20.2)
  - Departmental Recommendations Book II — Hispanic Studies – Multidisciplinary, 1970 Dec (Folder 20.3)
  - Educational Administration, 1971-1972 (Folder 20.4)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1971-1972 (Folder 20.5)